Ha Quyen

💌 quyentrankhanhha@gmail.com 📞 0417163232 🛮 in ha-quyen 🕥 quyentrankhanhha

➤ Ha Quyen's Portfolio

PROFILE

I'm confident in my approach to every opportunity as a student, driven by an eagerness to learn and adapt, which sets me apart. I might not be an expert in every area, but my dedication to mastering any given task is what defines me.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Software Developer Trainee, *Fatman Oy* ☑

05/2023 - present | Espoo, Finland

- Develop and maintain the product web.
- Work with teams to solve issues, find and implement efficiencies.
- Technologies consisting of JavaScript/ TypeScript, HTML/CSS, SCSS, Git, Svelte, SvelteKit, Svelte MUI, and Svelte Testing Library.

Front-end Student Staff, Keyloop (Finland) Oy 01/2022 - 09/2022 | Oulu, Finland

- Work on the client side for the internal company project
- Followed Agile methodology.
- Technologies consisting of JavaScript/ TypeScript, HTML/CSS, React, Material UI, Git, Mock Service Worker, React Router, Storybook, react-query, React Testing Library, and Cypress.

Associate Software Engineer, thuocsi.vn □

11/2021 - 01/2022 | Ho Chi Minh, Vietnam

- Participate in all Front-end development activities.
- Write quality code to implement software features or fix bugs.
- Technologies consisting of JavaScript, HTML/CSS, React, Material UI, NextJs, Gitlab, Jira

Software Developer Intern, thuocsi.vn □

08/2021 - 11/2021

PROJECTS

New portfolio 🗷

2023

- Building a new portfolio with React & Next.js. TypeScript, Tailwind CSS, shadon/ui, Framer Motion, React Email & Resend, Sanity, and Vercel hosting with CI/CD.
- Github Link □

E-Commerce

2023 - present

- Technologies consisting of Tailwindcss + HeadlessUI, State Management: React Query for async state and React Context, React Hook Form, React Router, Build tool with Vite, RestAPI, react.i18next, React Helmet for SEO, Story Book, and Unit Test
- GitHub Link

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Engineering, Information Technology, Oulu University of Applied Science

08/2019 - 03/2023 | Oulu, Finland

SKILLS

HTML/CSS | SCSS | JavaScript/TypeScript ReactJS | Redux | Nextis | Material UI | Svelte SvelteKit | Svelte MUI | Styled-components Svelte/ React Testing Library | Git | Restful API GraphQL | ExpressJs | NodeJs | Tailwind CSS Bootstrap | shadcn/ui | Sanity | SQL | NoSQL Python | Storybook

COURSES

Understanding TypeScript - 2022 Edition, *Udemy* 03/2022

Learn what TypeScript is, what its features are and how to use it, how it improves your JavaScript code and how it helps avoid nasty bugs and errors

Full stack open, University of Helsinki

05/2021

This course will introduce me to modern JavaScriptbased web development. The main focus is on building single page applications with ReactJS that use REST APIs built with Node.is.

CS50's Introduction to Computer Science, CS50 06/2020

- How to think algorithmically and solve programming problems efficiently
- Concepts like abstraction, algorithms, data structures, encapsulation, resource management, security, software engineering, and web development
- Familiarity in a number of languages, including C, Python, SQL, and JavaScript plus CSS and HTML